https://museumofaviation.org/privacy-policy/

AboutAbout the Museum of AviationIn the NewsAwards ReceivedFoundation Board of DirectorsBoard of GovernorsNational Board of AdvisorsMuseum StaffBoard Member AccessVisitPlan Your VisitMuseum Campus MapAdult Guided Tours and Team BuildingBirthday PartiesVirtual RealityEventsUpcoming Events & Education WorkshopsEvent Space RentalEvent Photos!Past EventsEducationAbout the National STEM AcademySaturday STEM LabsVirtual Field TripsGuided Tours and History Programs (Ages 4 – Adult)ACE and Wonder Wings (Pre K – 5th)TinkerTech (6th – 12th)Mission Quest Flight Simulators (6th – Adult)NASA Regional Educator Resource CenterEducator WorkshopsSTEM KitsTeacher of the Year ProgramSTEM Educator ConferenceSTARBASE ROBINSScoutsBirthday PartiesHomeschool STEM DaysSummer CampsNight at the MuseumExhibitsAircraft Exhibit GalleryAircraft ListAircraft ProjectsJoin & GiveDonateAdopt a SimVolunteer OpportunitiesDonor GuideShop & Event RegistrationConnectContactBlogTell Us How We’re DoingSubscribe for UpdatesFacebookTwitterYouTubeInstagramFlickr
Privacy PolicyHome Privacy Policy This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?When ordering or registering onsite, or online, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or other details to help you with your experience.When do we collect information?We collect information from you when you place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form or enter information on our site.How do we use your information?We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:    To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.    To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.    To quickly process your transactions.    To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.We do not sell or share donor, or visitor, information.  In addition, you may request to opt out of any or all of our correspondence by sending an email to information@museumofaviation.org requesting to be removed.How do we protect visitor information?Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.We use regular Malware Scanning.Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.Do we use ‘cookies’? We do not use cookies for tracking purposes. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders.Third Party Disclosure We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.Third party links We do not include or offer third party products or services on our website.GoogleGoogle’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=enWe have not enabled Google AdSense on our site but we may do so in the future.California Online Privacy Protection ActCalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. – See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpufAccording to CalOPPA we agree to the following: Users can visit our site anonymously. Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website. Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’, and can be easily be found on the page specified above.Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes: On our Privacy Policy PageUsers are able to change their personal information: By emailing us at information@museumofaviation.orgHow does our site handle do not track signals? We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking? It’s also important to note that we do not allow third party behavioral trackingCOPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation’s consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.Fair Information PracticesThe Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur: We will notify the users via email within 7 business daysWe also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.CAN SPAM ActThe CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.We collect your email address in order to:Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to ordersWe may also send you additional information related to your product and/or service.Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurredTo be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addressesIdentify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable wayInclude the physical address of our business or site headquartersMonitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quicklyAllow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each emailIf at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at information@museumofaviation.orgContacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.Museum of Aviation 1942 Heritage Blvd, Robins AFB, GA 31098 information@museumofaviation.orgLast Edited on 12-1-16
Are you ready to learn?Check out our youth and adult educational programs today!Get Started Now
